[
{
	"question": "Good morning",
	"A":"Do Widzenia",
	"B":"Dzień Dobry",
	"C":"Dobry Wieczór",
	"D":"Do zobaczenia",
	"correctAnswer":"B"
},
{
	"question": "Jak się masz",
	"A":"What's your name?",
	"B":"Where are you?",
	"C":"How are you?",
	"D":"How dare you?",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "Hi",
	"A":"Cześć",
	"B":"Pa",
	"C":"Na razie",
	"D":"Nara",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Good evening",
	"A":"Do widzenia",
	"B":"Dzień Dobry",
	"C":"Dobry Wieczór",
	"D":"Do zobaczenia",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "Apple",
	"A":"Gruszka",
	"B":"Jabłko",
	"C":"Śliwka",
	"D":"Pomidor",
	"correctAnswer":"B"
},
{
	"question": "Ja ____ jabłko",
	"A":"jem",
	"B":"jesz",
	"C":"jemy",
	"D":"jecie",
	"correctAnswer":"jem"
},
{
	"question": "Breakfast",
	"A":"Kolacja",
	"B":"Obiad",
	"C":"Podwieczorek",
	"D":"Śniadanie",
	"correctAnswer":"D"
},
{
	"question": "Dziękuję",
	"A":"Please",
	"B":"You're welcome",
	"C":"Thank you",
	"D":"Sure",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "Gdzie jesteś?",
	"A":"Where are you?",
	"B":"Who are you?",
	"C":"What is it?",
	"D":"Where are you from?",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Co to jest?",
	"A":"Where are you?",
	"B":"Who are you?",
	"C":"What is it?",
	"D":"Where are you from?",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "Jak masz na imię?",
	"A":"What's your name?",
	"B":"Where are you?",
	"C":"How are you?",
	"D":"How dare you?",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Do zobaczenia",
	"A":"Good morning",
	"B":"Farewell",
	"C":"See you soon",
	"D":"Good evening",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "Woda",
	"A":"Water",
	"B":"Wine",
	"C":"Vodka",
	"D":"Sea",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Proszę",
	"A":"Please",
	"B":"You're welcome",
	"C":"Thank you",
	"D":"Sure",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Nie ma za co",
	"A":"Please",
	"B":"You're welcome",
	"C":"Thank you",
	"D":"Sure",
	"correctAnswer":"B"
},
{
	"question": "Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter",
	"A":"Wiosna, Lato, Jesień, Zima",
	"B":"Lato, Wiosna, Zima,Jesień",
	"C":"Zima, Wiosna, Lato, Jesień",
	"D":"Wiosna, Zima, Jesień, Lato",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Ty ____ książkę",
	"A":"czytam",
	"B":"czytamy",
	"C":"czyta",
	"D":"czytasz",
	"correctAnswer":"D"
},
{
	"question": "Książka",
	"A":"Newspaper",
	"B":"Notebook",
	"C":"Book",
	"D":"Letter",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "To read",
	"A":"czytać",
	"B":"pisać",
	"C":"jeść",
	"D":"mówić",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "To eat",
	"A":"czytać",
	"B":"pisać",
	"C":"jeść",
	"D":"mówić",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
},
{
	"question": "To speak",
	"A":"czytać",
	"B":"pisać",
	"C":"jeść",
	"D":"mówić",
	"correctAnswer":"D"
},
{
	"question": "To write",
	"A":"czytać",
	"B":"pisać",
	"C":"jeść",
	"D":"mówić",
	"correctAnswer":"B"
},
{
	"question": "She speaks",
	"A":"Ona pisze",
	"B":"On mówi",
	"C":"On pisze",
	"D":"Ona mówi",
	"correctAnswer":"D"
},
{
	"question": "On ____ książkę",
	"A":"pisze",
	"B":"piszę",
	"C":"piszemy",
	"D":"pisz",
	"correctAnswer":"A"
},
{
	"question": "Ja, Ty, On, Ona",
	"A":"I, He, She, You",
	"B":"He, You, I, She",
	"C":"I, You, He, She",
	"D":"You, I, She, He",
	"correctAnswer":"C"
}
]